Guide to the Robert Wilson papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I
  - Subseries I.4: Production Files
    - Life and Times of Dave Clark
      - Parsifal -- Administrative -- Administrative--Kassel--Cancellation--Litigation -- Technical--Decor -- Programs, Flyers, Exhibition catalogs -- Press, Printed -- Poles Project see Theatre Activity -- Prologue to the Fourth Act of Deafman Glance see Program -- Prologue, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 180)
      - Program Prolog: Now: Overture for A Deafman -- Press -- Also filed here: Prologue to the Fourth Act of Deafman Glance, Overture to the Fourth Act of Deafman Glance; -- See also Deafman Glance1978-1982 -- 1986, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 181)
      - Quartet -- Stuttart--Administrative -- Stuttart--Proposal, H. Muller notes, Research -- Stuttart--Programs -- American Repertory Theatre--Administrative -- American Repertory Theatre--Speech notes -- American Repertory Theatre--Production -- American Repertory Theatre--Programs -- Press, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 182)
      - Relative Calm -- Administrative -- Research -- Technical Storyboards -- Programs -- Press, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 183)
      - Salome -- Administrative -- Wilson's notes, research -- Technical -- Production -- Programs -- Press, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 184)
      - Theatre Activity -- Administrative -- Research -- Programs, Flyers -- Press -- Videos, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 185)
  - Subseries I.5: Videos
    - General -- Breakfast Table--Storyboards -- New Video project--Storyboards, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 186)
    - Spaceman -- Administrative -- Flyers, Programs, Announcements -- Printed, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 187)
    - Stations (Video 13) -- Administrative, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 188)
    - Stations (Video 13) -- Administrative, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 189)
    - Stations (Video 13) -- Storyboards, tech scripts, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 190)
    - Stations -- Research -- Note: See also Flat, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 191)
    - Stations -- Research, production, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 192)
    - Stations -- Flyers -- Press -- Printed, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 193)
    - Video 50 -- Administrative -- Administrative--Artservice, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 194)
    - Video 50 -- Research -- Technical -- Music, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 195)
    - Video 50 -- Storyboards and notes--Artservice -- Storyboards and notes, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 196)
    - Video 50 -- Production -- Programs and Flyers -- Press Packets -- Press -- Printed -- Art, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 197)
  - Subseries I.6: Art
    Herein are filed fliers, brochures, catalogs, announcements, invitations, clippings, reviews, cards, etc. related to exhibitions and works of Wilson's art and articles about Wilson's art in general. Exhibits of art related to a production are filed with the production files.
    - Art Exhibitions 1967-1979 -- Press -- Invitations -- Printed Material1967-1979, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 198)
    - Art Exhibitions 1980-1982 -- Press -- Invitations -- Printed Material1980-1982, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 199)
    - Art Exhibitions 1983-1984 -- Press -- Invitations -- Printed Material1983-1984, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 200)
    - Art Exhibitions 1985-1988 -- Press -- Invitations -- Printed Material1985-1988, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 201)
    - Art-Printed, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 202)
    - Art-Printed -- Note: See also Oversize -- Clipping Files, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 203)
  - Subseries I.7: Clippings Files
    There are two main sequences of clippings files: 1972-Dec. 1987, and the scrapbooks of clippings, Feb. 1964-June 1981. 4 v.& 2 v. (1974)
    - 1972-1978, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 204)
    - 1970-79 Artservice, 1981-Japanese, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 205)
    - 1964-1971, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 206)
    - 1973-6/83, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 207)
    - 7/83-1986, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 208)
    - 1984-3/31/84, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 209)
    - 4/1-10/31/84, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 210)
    - Fall,Winter 1984 -- 11/1-12/31/84, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 211)
    - 1/1/85-4/31/85, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 212)
    - 5/1-9/30/85, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 213)
    - 10/85-12/31/85, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 214)
    - 1/1/86-5/31/86, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 215)
    - 6/86-9/30/86, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 216)
    - 10/86, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 217)
    - 11/86-12/86, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 218)
    - 1/87-3/87, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 219)
    - 4/87-6/87, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 220)
    - 7/87-12/87 -- Clipping Binders, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 221)
    - 1. 11/64 - 12/69 -- 2. 1/70-3/71 -- 3. 4/71 -- 4. 5/1/71-5/19/71 -- 5. 5/2/71-6/2/71 -- 6. 6/2/71-6/10/71, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 222)
    - 7. 6/17/71-2/22/72 -- 8. 3/15/72-9/4/79 -- 9. 9/5/72-9/28/72 -- 10. 10/72-12/72 -- 11. 1/73-7/73 -- 12. 8/73-11/14/73, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 223)
    - 13. 11/15/73 - 12/31/737 -- 14. 1/74-4/74 -- 15. 5/74-7/74 -- 16. 8/74-12/74 -- 17. 1/75-2/75 -- 18. 3/1/75-3/23/75, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 224)
    - 19. 3/24/75 - 3/31/75 -- 20. 4/75-5/75 -- 21. 6/75-10/75 -- 22. 11/75-12/75 -- 23. 1/76-3/75 -- 24. 4/76-6/76, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 225)
    - 25. 7/76 - 10/76 -- 26. 11/76-12/76 -- 27. 1/77-5/77 -- 28. 6/77-5/78 -- 29. 6/78-12/78, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 226)
    - 30. 1/79 - 2/79 -- 31. 3/79-6/79 -- 32. 7/79-12/17/79 -- 33. 1/80-9/80 -- 34. 9/80 -- Audio / Visual Material, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 227)
  - Subseries I.8: Audio/Visual Material
    - Cassette- Radio broadcast on France culture, Nov. 1988. -- Including interview with R. Wilson. -- General Printed Material, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 228)
    - Undated and miscellaneous articles about Robert Wilson (see also Flat) -- Excerpts from reviews, 1969-1980 -- 1973-79, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 229)
    - 1980, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 230)
    - 1981-85, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 231)
    - 1986-1989, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 232)
    - Unidentified, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 233)
  - Subseries I.9: Posters
    Mapcase 15-12-3/4 -- * Indicates oversized (on table in Cage 26, stack 15) -- typog. = designed in typography with no illustration
    - Alcestis
      - Photograph of Robert Wilson, *Festival d'Automne, Bobigny, 1986, (47.5 x 31.5 in. )
      - American Repertory Theatre, Cambridge MA, 1986
      - Photograph of classic Belgrade Festival, Belgrade, 1974
      - Lithograph, [n.p.], [n.d.], (38.5 x 26.5 in. )
        [ not by Wilson]
    - the CIVIL warS
      - Freiburger Klassik Konzerte, Sparkasse, 1982, (typog. 34x24 in. )
      - Exhibition of Drawings for the CIVIL warS, Paris, 1982, (25.5 x 18 in. )
        [dwg and lettering by RW]
      - Ill: photo of bird; encapsulated, Schouwburg, 1983, (25 x 17 in. )
      - Ill: photo of bird; encapsulated, Schouwburg, 1983, (46.5 x 32.5 in. )
      - Ill: dwg. not by RW, Teatro dell' Opera di Roma, 1984, (28 x 12 in. )
      - Ill: dwg. not by RW, Teatro dell' Opera di Roma, 1984, (39.5 x 27.5 in. )
      - Production and exhibition of dwgs.; ill: photo of face, Cologne, 1984, (34 x 23 in. )
      - Kolner Kulturprisma: list of events for Jan 20-30 1984, Cologne, 1984, (24 x 34 in. typog, )
      - RW Performance and exhibition of dwgs from the CIVIL warS; ill: picture of RW; encapsulated, Halle, [n.d.], (36 x 25.5 in. )
      - [The Knee Plays]RW dwg., Walker Art Center, 1984, (22x15 in. )
      - [The Knee Plays] ill: photo of production (encapsulated), Walker Art Center, 1984, (30 x 23 in. )
      - [The Knee Plays] ill: RW dwg/photo, Bobigny, 1985, (24 x 17 in. )
      - [The Knee Plays] signed "Happy Birthday to Bob" by cast, Bobigny., [n.d.]
      - [The Knee Plays] color: ill: production photograph, Teatro Malibran, Venice Festival, October 1985, (39 x 13 in. )
      - [The Knee Plays] color: typog., Palazzo dei Congressi, Bologna, Oct. 1985, (39 x 13 in. )
    - De Materie
      - Color ill: drawing by Wilson, *Nederlandse Opera, Amsterdam, June 1989, (46.5 x 33 in. )
    - Deafman Glance
      - Holland Festival, Holland, 1971, (24 x 33 in. typog, )
      - [Le Regard du Sourd] ill: photo of production; encapsulated[n.p.], 1971, 24 x 15.5 in.
    - Death Destruction and Detroit
      - Ill: dwg of dinosaurs; encapsulated, Berlin, 1979, (20 x 14 in. )
      - Ill: dwg of dinosaurs, [proof?]; image, Berlin, 1079, (ca. 19 x 13 in. )
      - Typog., West-Berliner Buhnen, 8-17 Feb. 1979, ( 24 x 33 in. )
    - Dialog/Curious George
      - Ill: non-RW dwg, Florence, Teatro Regionale Toscano, Oct/Dec 1977 season, (28 x 13 in. )
      - Ill: production photo, *Rotterdam, 1980, (46 x 32.5 in )
      - Ill: dwg, in white on grey, New York, June 24-29, 1980, (24 x19 in. )
      - Ill: white, signed by Christopher Knowles, encapsulated, New York, 1980, (25 x19 in. )
      - *Ill: green, New York, 1980, ( 44.5 x 32.5 in. )
        [ ]
      - *Ill: green, signed by Christopher Knowles, encapsulated. New York, 1980, (44.5 x 32.5 in. )
      - *Ill: multicolor, New York, 1980, (44.5 x 32.5 in. )
      - *Ill: signed by Robert Wilson., New York, 1980
    - Doktor Faustus
      - Typog., Teatro alla Scala, Milan, 1989, ( 39.5 x 27.5 in. )
      - Color, ill: drawing by Wilson, Teatro alla Scala, Milan, 1989, (38.5 x 27 in. )
    - $ Value of Man
      - Ill: RW dwg; encapsulated, BAM, May 1975, (24 x 15 in. )
      - Dublin Theatre Festival Conference: The Creative impulse in modern theatre. Ill in color: drawing (not by Wilson), Dublin, 1988(?), (23.5 x 16 )
    - Edison
      - Ill: photo of RW from production, Milano, 1979, (39 x 27 in )
      - Schedule of Teatro alla Scala; typog, Scala, Oct., (15 x 11 in. )
      - Schedule of Teatro alla Scala; typog, Scala, Oct., (40 x 27.5 in. )
      - Typog. schedule, Theatre National Populaire, 1979/80 season, (35 x 12 )
    - Einstein on the Beach
      - Production photo; encapsulated, Metropolitan Opera, 21 Nov 1986, (41 x 20.5 in. )
      - *Production photo of two actors jumping, Rotterdam, 1976, (46 x 33 in typog, )
      - Title and picture only, BAM, 11-23 Dec 1984, (37 x 25 in. )
      - Ill: silhouette from production, BAM, 11-23 Dec 1984, (42.25 x 34 in. )
    - Festival d' Automne a Paris
      - Non-RW dwg, Paris, 1972, (23.5 x 15.5 in. )
      - Non-RW dwg in brown/black, Paris, 1972, ( 23.5 x 16 in. )
      - Photo of RW, Paris, 1972, (24 x 16 in. )
    - The Golden Windows [Die Golden Fenster]
      - Ill: RW dwg, Munich, 1982, (24 x 34 in. )
      - Exhibition of dwgs; ill: RW dwg, Munich, 1982, (34 x 24 in. )
      - Muncher Kammerspiele 1982/83 season, typog. Munich, 1982, (34 x 24 in )
    - I Was Sitting on My Patio This Guy Appeared I Thought I Was Hallucinating
      - Ill: photo of L. Childs' back, Walker Art Center, Edyth Bush Theatre, April 1977, (15 x 9 in. )
      - Photo of L. Childs' back, Cherry Lane Theater, 1977, (35 x 22 in )
      - Photo of L. Childs' back, San Francisco, Veteran's Auditorium, April 1977, (22 x 15 in. )
      - *Production photo, Theater II, 1978, (50.75 x 35.5 in. )
      - *Typog (word grid), Amsterdam, 1978, (46 x 32.5 in. )
      - Typog., Atelier de Geneve, 1978, (39 x 26 in. )
      - Production photo of L. Childs lying down, Royal Court, June 1978, (20 x 13 in. )
      - Production photo of L. Childs lying down, Milano, Feb 1978, (38.5 x 27 in. )
      - Production photo of L. Childs lying down; encapsulated, Paris, Theatre de la Renaissance, 1978, (32 x 16.5 )
        [Also, 4 copies of the same poster, not encapsulated]
    - A Letter for Queen Victoria
      - Typog., Spoleto, Teatro Caro Melisso, 1974, (27 x 14 in. )
      - Typog; two parts each, Spoleto, Teatro Caro Melisso, 1974, (24 x 32 in. )
      - Photo from production, with banner, Festival d'Automne a Paris, 1974, (39.5 x 27 in. )
      - Without title or banner, Festival d'Automne a Paris, 1974
      - With title, Festival d'Automne a Paris, 1974
      - Banner only, Festival d'Automne a Paris, 1974, (ca. 31 x 7 in. )
        [cut to fit across corner of poster above]
      - Production photo; encapsulated, Palais Mediterranee, Nov 1974, (23 x 14 in. )
      - Hand lettering, New York, ANTA Theatre, 1974, (32 x 14 in. )
      - Typog., Lyon, Centre Dramatique National de Lyon, Nov 1974, (30 x 12 in. )
    - The Life & Times of Joseph Stalin
      - Photo of chairs, Holland, 1973, (34 x 24 in. )
      - Photo of chairs; encapsulated, BAM, Dec 1973, (23.5 x 17.5 in. )
      - Without title, BAM, 1973, (34 x 24 in. )
    - The Life & Times of Sigmund Freud
      - Dwg; grey ink, BAM, Dec 1969, (35 x 23 in. )
      - Dwg; black ink, BAM, Dec 1969, (35 x 23 in. )
      - Dwg; black ink, BAM, Dec 1969, (38 x 25 in. )
      - Dwg; black/grey/white on taupe; signed "after engraving by William Blake/R. Wilson 70/300"; framed, BAM, 1969, (34 x 25 in. )
        [SHELVED in MAPCASE 13-8-7]
      - Drawing, Lyon, Centre Dramatique National de Lyon, 1974/75, (15 x 20 in. )
    - Man in the Raincoat
      - Production photograph, Amsterdam, Musiek Theatre, 1986/87, (23 x 17 in. )
    - Le martyre de Saint Sebastien
      - Photographs of cast, encapsulated, Bobigny, Theatre National Opera de Paris, 25 March -16 April 1988, (25 x 16.5 in )
    - Medea
      - Ill: vertical black stripe, Opera de Paris, 1984, (19 x 13 in. )
      - *Ill, Opera de Paris, 1984, (45.5 x 30 in. )
      - Typog, Opera de Lyon, 1984, (23 x 15 in. )
      - *Typog. Opera de Lyon, 1984, (46 x 30.5 in. )
      - Typog. Nancy, Festival Mondial du Theatre Universitaire de Nancy, France, du 21 Avril du 2 Mai 1971, (33 x 22.5 in. )
      - Non-RW photo, Olympic Arts Festival, Los Angeles, 1984, (34x22 in. )
    - La nuit d'avant le jour
      - *Poster for season including this production, Opera de Paris Bastille, 1989, (48 x 38.5 in. )
    - Orlando
      - Drawing by Wilson (b/w); schedule annotated in ms, Schaubuhne, Berlin, Nov. 1989, (33 x 12 in. )
    - Salome
      - Typog., Milano, 1987, (15 x 11 in. )
    - Salome
      - Typog., Milano, 1987, (39.5 x 27.75 in. )
      - Gold design on crimson; encapsulated, Shiraz Festival, Persepolis, 1972, (41.25 x 27 in. )
    - Swan Song
      - Black and yellow photo [from production?], Munchner Kammerspiele, 1989, (23.5 x 33 in. )
      - Color, ill: drawing by Wilson, Munchner Kammerspiele, 1989, (23.5 x 33 in. )
      - Photo of the Rinpoche. Benefit for Dudjon Rinpoche, Town Hall, 1976, (29 x 23 in. )
    - Wilson Solo Performances
      - *Typog, Netherlands, [n.d.], (46 x 32.5 in. )
      - Typog., Chiesa di Saint Teresa, [n.d.], (21 x 31 in. )
      - Commune di Milano Settore Educazione Series titled "La Parola alla Danza: tre incontri con i maestri della danza contemporanea": Robert Wilson: Work, Milan, 1968-1989, 17 May 1989.
      - Colaiste Mhuire Hall Text and drawing by Wilson; photo of Wilson, Dublin Theatre Festival, 1988(?), (16 x 23.5 in. )
    - Exhibitions
      - Dwg in pastels, Stuttgart, [n.d.], (34 x 24 in )
      - Photo:Robert Wilson: From a Theater of Images, SUNY Purchas, 1980
      - Death Destruction and Detroit. Printed on both sides for mailing, [n.p.], 24 x 18 in.
      - Amerikanische Zeichnungen; typog., Munich, 1982, (33 x 25.5 in. )
      - MOMA An International Survey of Recent Painting and Sculpture, New York. .Ill: non- RW, 1984, (25 x 39 in )
      - Dwgs for Medea, Parsifal and Alceste; ill: dwg from Alceste, Act II, Scene I, Munich, 1987, (24 x 31 in. )
  - Subseries I.10: Oversize Material
    - Production Files
      - the CIVIL warS --Press, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 234)
      - the CIVIL warS--Printed -- Deafman Glance--Press -- Einstein on the Beach--Printed -- The Forest--Printed -- Art -- Printed, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 235)
  - Subseries I.11: Flat Material
    - Cataloged Correspondence
      - Scrapbook of photocopies of correspondence and conversations between R. Wilson and Dallas Pratt, [n.p.], [n.d.]
  - Subseries I.12: Production Files
    - the CIVIL warS
      - , Germany, Frieburg Workshop, 1982
      - Knee Plays--Press, [n.p.], [n.d.]
    - The Forest
      - Press, [n.p.], [n.d.]
    - I Was Sitting on My Patio This Guy Appeared I Thought I Was Hallucinating
      - Press, [n.p.], [n.d.]
    - Life and Times of Joseph Stalin
      - Recording of Stalin, [n.p.], [n.d.]
    - Overture (Ka Mountain)
      - Programs, [n.p.], [n.d.]
  - Subseries I.13: Videos
    - Stations
      - Research, [n.p.], [n.d.]
  - Subseries I.14: General Printed Material
    Herein are filed printed materials related to survey's of Wilson's career as a whole, and other miscellaneous printed materials.
    - Undated and Miscellaneous articles about R. Wilson, [n.p.], [n.d.]
- Series II
  Oversize folders located at end of Series II
  - Subseries II.1: Press Files
    - File 1: Press, January 1- April 30, 1988 (Box 236)
    - File 2: Press, [n.p.], May 1 - June 30, 1988 (Box 237)
    - File 3: Press, [n.p.], July 1 - December 31, 1988 (Box 238)
  - Subseries II.2: Research Files
    - File 4: King Lear Research, UCLA, 1985 (Box 239)
    - File 5: The Forest Research, [n.p.], 1988
    - File 6: Black Rider Research, [n.p.], 1990, (1 Oversize folder, )
    - File 7: Le Martyre de Saint Sebastien Research, [n.p.], 1988, (1 Oversize folder, )
      [Oversize folder]
    - File 1: Parsifal (Cancelled, 1982 Kassel Production) Research -- A. Xeroxes of Parsifal drawings by RW -- B. Costume research -- C. Line entrances and scene images -- D. Images -- E. Swan research -- F. Librettos, misc. -- G. Xeroxes of RW's blackbook notes on Parsifal -- H. Submarine research -- I. General Ideas --, [n.p.], 1982
    - File 2: Parsifal Research -- A. Xeroxes of pictures -- B. Letters regarding Kassell cancellation -- C. Photos of perspective singles -- D. Various visual material -- E. Miscellaneous material -- F. Plant research -- G. General ideas -- H. General ideas -- I. Libretto material -- J. General ideas -- K. Xeroxes of RW Parsifal drawings -- L. Production notes, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 240)
  - Subseries II.3: Books
    - Miscellaneous Research, 1986 -- A. Christopher Columbus project research -- B. Black Rider early project research -- C. Alceste research -- D. Alceste research -- E. Alcestis research --, [n.p.], 1986 (Box 241, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Research 1987 -- A. Christopher Columbus/ Leonardo Ballada research -- B. Christopher Columbus/ Alitalia Magazine -- C. Research material suggested by A.R.T. -- D. Jonathan Carroll, Bones of the Moon -- E. Antonin Artaud, The Umbilicus of Limbo -- F. August Strindberg, Coram Populo -- G. Mausoleums -- H. Hans Christian Meiser, Ludwig II -- I. Das Vittoriale Der Italiener -- J. David Mamet short plays -- K. Charles Mee scripts -- L. Pocohontas research -- M. 3 x 3 poem book -- N. Napolean film research --, [n.p.], 1987 (Box 242, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Production Books -- A. Alcestis, script 1986 -- B. Arabian Nights, proposal, 1986 -- C. Black Rider, proposal, 1986 -- D. De Materie Score, I-IV (two sets), 1988 - Oversize folder -- E. Edison storyboards, 1979 -- F. The Forest, proposal, 1986 -- G. The Golden Windows, music parts, 1982 - Oversize folder -- --1. Viola/Cello -- --2. Percussion -- --3. Oboe/ French Horn -- --4. Violin I/ II -- --5. Piano -- --6. Conductor -- --7. Harpsichord -- H. The Golden Windows, script 1985 -- I. Patio, storyboards, 1978 --, [n.p.], 1978-1986 (Box 243, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Production Books: -- A.Murder (Deafman Glance), storyboards, 1981 -- B.CIVIL warS/ French Section, storyboards -- C.CIVIL warS/ general information -- D.CIVIL warS, sound running book, 1983, [n.p.], 1981-1983 (Box 244, Folder 1)
    - A. CIVIL waeS, television story boards -- B. Second script (two sets), [n.p.], 1982 (Box 246)
    - A. CIVIL warS/ Knee Plays, general production book -- B.CIVIL warS/ Knee Plays, music parts: -- --1. Tuba -- --2.Trombone -- --3. Baritone Saxophone, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 246)
    - A. CIVIL warS/Knee Plays, music parts, continued: -- --1. -- Percussion -- --2. Trumpet 1 -- --3. Trumpet 2 -- --4. Tenor -- Saxophone, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 247)
    - Miscellaneous Research -- --A.Alcestis rehearsal schedule, 1987 -- --B.DDD II, general research material, 1987 -- --C.DDD II, Son of Sam research material, 1987 -- --D.DDD II, Son of Sam research material, 1987 -- --E.DDD II, general research material, 1987 -- --F.Napollean articles, 1987 -- --G.The Forest, David Byrne scenario, 1987 -- --H.RW notes with R. Rutkowski, July 1987 -- --I.Cosmopollitan Greetings, Bessie Smith research, 1988, [n.p.], 1987/1988 (Box 248, Folder 1)
  - Subseries II.4: Scores
    - DDD Scores (Jerry Frankel, Composer) 1979 -- --A.DDD, original score and tape, 1979 -- --B.DDD, scores, 1979 -- --C.DDD, parts for voices, [n.p.], 1979 (Box 249, Folder 2)
  - Subseries II.5: Crete File
    - Regarding RW's Imprisonment -- --A.Miscellaneous letters -- --B.Miscellaneous telegrams -- --C.Miscellaneous notebooks -- --D.Miscellaneous Legal documents -- --E.Miscellaneous RW notes from prison -- --F.Letter from Daniel Stern (BHF approval necessary, in Vault, filed in Box 255), [n.p.], [n.d.] (Box 250, Folder 3)
  - Subseries II.6: Projects
    - Projects: -- --A.Alcestis -- --B.DDD II -- --C.French Revolution -- --D.Proposed fellowship in India -- --E.King Lear workshop/ UCLA -- --F.Quartet -- --G.RW readings, script -- --H.Paolo Soleri Foundation -- --I.SSDC interview, 1987 -- --J.Amherst/ Goethe Foundation theatre colloquium, [n.p.], 1987 (Box 251, Folder 4)
  - Subseries II.7: Programs and Literatures
    - Recent Programs and Literatures (loose) -- --A.King Lear, Frankfurt 1990, program -- --B.Theater Heute, June 1990 (feature on Black Rider) -- --C.National Forum, Summer 1990 -- --D.Feigen Gallery Brochure, September 1990 -- --E.Opera News, September 1990 -- --F.Robert Wilson's Vision by Trevor Fairbrother -- --G.Robert Wilson's Vision, brochure to Boston show -- --H.Robert Wilson's Vision, AT&T press kit -- --I.Stuff Magazine, insert on RW, April 1991 -- --J.When We Dead Awaken, ART 1991, program -- --K.When We Dead Awaken, ART 1991, program book -- --L.Parsifal, Hamburg 1991, program -- --M.Zeit Magazine, edited by RW, July 1991 -- --N.Die Zauberflote, Paris 1991, program -- --O.The Knee Plays, Minnesota 1985, program book, [n.p.], 1985-1991 (Box 252, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Old Press -- --A.Cahiers Renaud Barrault, 1972 -- --B.Performance Texts & Documents (conference), 1980 -- --C.Pratt Dance Workshop, 1965, program -- --D.Theater, Fall/Winter 1986 (Alcestis) -- --E.Sprache im Technischen Zeitalter, 1979 -- --F.Miscellaneous articles from 1970s, [v.p.], 1965-1980 (Box 253, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Research: -- --A.Brothers research -- --B.Frederico Garcia Lorca plays -- --C.The Great Campaign, Arnold Sundgaard -- --D.Holderlin project, music of Giovanni Sollima, [n.p.], [n.d.] (Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous: -- --A.Transcription of Theatre interview w/ RW, 1975 -- --B.BHF corporate-- Letter from Jane Yockel, November 1977 -- --C.CIVIL warS, early project description, September 1982 -- Budget Documentation, [n.p.], 1975-1982 (Folder 4)
  - Subseries II.8: Budget Documentation
    - Miscellaneous Budget Documentation -- --A.1978 - 1979 Einstein on the Beach budget correspondences -- --B.1976 - 1978 Einstein on the Beach financial problems -- --C.CIVIL warS drawings information -- --D.CIVIL warS budget documents (in French) -- --E.Miscellaneous CIVIL warS budget notes (in French) -- --F.Miscellaneous CIVIL warS budget correspondences (French) -- --G.Miscellaneous CIVIL warS contracts (in French) -- --H.CIVILL warS 1986, listing of production book discs -- --I.CIVIL warS 1982, Los Angeles budget -- --J.CIVIL warS 1980 - 1981, budget, [v.p.], 1976-1986 (Box 254, Folder 5)
  - Subseries II.9: Miscellaneous Contracts